<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="faqs">
		<item>Version 1.4.9 launches with improved rendering, reliability and performance!</item>,
        <item>As of Version 1.4.7, themes and backups are now stored in /Android/data/com.sunnykwong.omc/files/ instead of /.OMCThemes/. WARNING: THEMES AND BACKUPS NO LONGER SURVIVE UNINSTALL, so please move your backups and customizations to another folder *before* you uninstall!</item>,
		<item>If you have old customizations and backups, please save them to a safe place on your SD card.  When you need to use them, copy them to the /Android/data/com.sunnykwong.omc/files/ folder.  After you finish backing everything up, you can delete all the files in the .OMCThemes folder (with a dot).</item>,
		<item>The paid version features a one-second refresh.  While the one-second refresh results in higher battery drain, it adds a nice dynamic quality to clocks with a second hand.</item>,
		<item>Clocks have tags on the theme picker screen.  Tap on a tag to understand what it means!</item>,
		<item>Not finding your favorite clock?  OMC comes with just a few initially.  To get the full clock collection, tap on \'Download Full Online Collection\' when you\'re in the theme picker screen.</item>,
		<item>To back up or share your changes, on \'Set Widget Theme\', long-press a theme and select \'email theme\'.</item>,
		<item>OMC supports battery levels.  Some of the widgets contain battery indicators in surprising ways - browse around and experiment!</item>,
		<item>You can specify a timezone or time offset for each clock independently of the device setting.  This allows for nice home/travel clock scenarios.</item>,
		<item>OMC lets you send your favorite personalizations to Xaffron!  Tap and hold a clock on the theme picker screen, then select \'Email Tweaked Theme\' to send to me.</item>,
		<item>OMC allows theme personalization on the phone.  Try moving each layer around, changing colors and toggling visibility!</item>,
		<item>Theme personalization overwrites dynamic elements (changing colors, positions, text, etc).  To make fine-tuned changes to dynamic elements, fire up a text editor on your phone or computer and look at the contents of the 00control.json file.</item>,
		<item>The paid version now features 8 widget sizes.  Not all themes work well with all widget sizes, but feel free to experiment! The newer ones look particularly good in the square and vertical widgets.</item>,
		<item>Too many widget sizes?  Tap on \'Toggle Widget Sizes\' and disable the ones you don\'t want.  Remember to reboot your phone to apply changes!</item>,
		<item>Comments? Complaints? Donations?  Tap on the \'Contact Xaffron\' box to send me a message.  I\'ll get back to you ASAP!</item>,
		<item>Did you know that you can delete any clock you don\'t like by long-pressing on a clock?  If you want it back, simply select \'Re-Get Starter Clock Pack\' and you\'re right back where you started.</item>,
		<item>Tap-to-Launch now allows you to set \'Do nothing\', which is great for avoiding accidental taps.  Tapping on the top left corner of the widget always brings you back to this screen.</item>,
		<item>Want more quotes/different text?  I hear you!  For now, use a text editor on the 00control.json files (it\'s easy, I promise).  Otherwise, expect enhanced \'Personalization\' features in the next couple of versions!</item>,
		<item>Have an idea for a cool clock widget?  Tap \'Contact Xaffron\' and let me know. I don\'t bite!</item>,
		<item>Which clock is your favorite?  Let me know via \'Contact Xaffron\'!  This will help me archive less popular widgets and keep the application size manageable.</item>,
		<item>Did you know that there is a support thread on XDA-Developers?  I monitor questions on that board on a daily basis.  http://forum.xda-developers.com/showthread.php?t=807929</item>
    </string-array>
    
</resources>